DAVID BALDUS PAPERS (APAP329) 1965-2011
M. E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives
- General Research Materials, 1985-2011; 5; 3.4
  - The United States Law Week, Unopened, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Vathele Publishing, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - "Black immigrants and black natives attending selective colleges and universities in the united states." By D. Massey, M. Mooney, and K. Torres, 2007 February (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - "Is the Magic still there? The use of heckman two-step correction for selection Bias in criminology" by Shawn Bushway, Brian D. johnson, and Lee Ann Slocum, 2007 March (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - "Pedagogy of the Suppressed: A class on race and the death penalty." by Phyliss goldfarb, 2007 March (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - National Law Journal article on federal death penalty, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Onwuachi-Willig, Angela, 2007; Undated (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - "A rare and Arbitrary Fate:Being mandatorily sentenced to death in Trinidad and Tobago- A summary of the report to the death penalty project" By Roger Hood and Florence Seemungal, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - "Life and Death Decision: Prosecutorial discretion and capital punishment in Missouri." By K.Y. Barnes and D. Sloss, 2008 March (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - "Two Worlds far apart: Black-white differences in Beliefs about why African American men are Disproportionately imprisoned." by james D. unnever, 2008 May (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - "Reassessing Race disparities in Maryland Capital Cases" By Raymond Paternoster and Robert Brame, 2008 October (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Ethnicity and Race, 2008 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - ethnicity and Race, 2008 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - ethnicity and Race, 2008 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - ethnicity and Race, 2008 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - "The malign effects of drug and crime control policies on black americans" by Michael Tonry and Matthew melewski, 2008 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - "Neighborhood racial context and perceptions of police-Based racial discrimination amoung black youth by E.A. Stewart, R.K. Brunson, and R.L. Simons, 2009 June (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Abortion link to Crime rate- John J. Donohue III and Steven D. Levitt, "The impact of legalized abortion on Crime.", 2009 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Bias Theory Articles, 2009 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - "Empathetic identification and Punitiveness" by J.D. Unnever and F.T. Cullen, 2009 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - "Place matters (most): An Empirical study of prosecutorial Decision making in death-Eligible cases" by katherine barnes, David Sloss, and Stephen Thaman., 2009 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - No Race effect Articles, 2009 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - "What Explains persistent Racial disproportionality in minnesota's prison and jail populations?" by Richard Frase, 2009 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Citations from Bill Quigley Huffington post piece., 2010 September (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Claimed Race effects articles, 2010 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Research on Employment law and Discrimination, 2010 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - American Bar Association Death Penalty Representation project, Undated (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Appendix to the final report of the Pennsylvania Supreme court on Racial and gender bias in the justice system (1 of 2), Undated (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Appendix to the final report of the Pennsylvania Supreme court on Racial and gender bias in the justice system (2 of 2), Undated (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Cases that are Discrimination-related but no Title VIII issues, Undated (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Criminal Reporter, Undated (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Franklin E. Zimring and James Zuehl, "Victim injury and death in Urban Robbery: A Chicago study, Undated (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Glenn L. pierce and Michael L. Radelet, "The role and Consequence of the death Penalty in American Politics.", Undated (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Kent Greenwalt, "Objectivity and Law", Undated (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Law Week, Undated (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - "Mortgage lending discrimination: A review of existing evidence" edited by margery Austin Turner, Undated (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Philosophers- Kant, Mill,Plato,Rousseau, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Research on sentencing guidelines, Undated (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - samuel R. Sommers- CV and Research articles, Undated (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - State cases dealing with McCleskey for Columbia paper, Undated (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Willie simmons V. State of Missouri twenty second judicial circuit (1 of 3), Undated (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - willie simmons V. State of Missouri twenty second judicial circuit (2 of 3), Undated (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - willie Simmons V. State of missouri Twenty second judicial circuit (3 of 3), Undated (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Teaching, 1969-2011; 6; 8
  This series is arranged chronologically.
  The teaching series and subsequent subseries encompasses Professor Baldus time teaching as a law Professor and his scholarly interests.
  - Admiralty Law, 1992-1999; 6.1; 0.3
    This subseries is arranged chronologically.
    This subseries covers class materials such as correspondence, syllabi and teaching notes on Admiralty Law.
    - Bills of luding, 1997; Undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence,Syllabi,class materials, exams, 1997 Spring; 1999 spring (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Course materials- selected readings from "Pictoral history of American ships" by John and Alice Durant(1953), Undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - exams- final exams, 1994 spring (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - exams, 1997 spring (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - John Mcphee readings, Undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Mortgage and liens, 1993; 1999; Undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Notes on readings- Schoenbaum, pat bauer, Sam Fohr, Undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Readings, 1999; Undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Teaching Notes, 1999; Undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Teaching notes- exxon Valdez, Wrecks, Salvage., 1999; Undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Teaching notes-Jurisdiction, 1992-1994; 1997-1999 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Teaching notes, readings, 1999; Undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Teaching notes, Readings, 1999; Undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Capital Punishment Symposium, 1998-2011; 6.2; 3.7
    This series is arranged alphabetically.
    The Capital Punishment Symposium subseries contains course materials, abstracts, and other course supplemental materials.
    - 2008 Miscellary- Jury selection (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - A sampling of abstracts from research papers, 2007-2008 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - A sampling of abstracts from research papers, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Capital punishment and the judical process, second edition, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - case chart or table, 2004 fall (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - chapter 6- miller-el, jury selection, 2004 fall (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Chapter 9-teaching notes, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - China Developments, 2006 fall (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Class list, 2004 fall (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Constitutional requirement of "important jury" in capital cases- assignment by Ryan Struve, 2003 fall (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Course marterials-2007 supplement to Radelet and Vandiver 1988 Capital Punishment Biblography, 2007-2008 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - course marterials-2007 supplement to Radelet and Vandiver 1988 Capital Punishment Biblography, 2007-2008 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Course marterials-2007 supplement to Radelet and Vandiver 1988 Capital Punishment Biblography, 2007-2008 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Course materials- "A Broken system: The persistent patterns of reversals of death sentences in the united States" (2003), Undated (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Course materials- A sampling of abstracts from research papers, 2007-2008 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - course materials- "A self-teaching guide to The Bluebook: A uniform system of citation" (2001), Undated (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Course materials- America's experiment with capital punishment, James Acker (2003), Undated (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Course materials- Annotated Biblography, 2009 spring (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Course materials- Annotated biblography, 2009 spring (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Course materials- annotated Biblography (bound), 2009 Spring (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Course materials- articles by James Acker and Charles Lanier, Undated (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Course materials- capital punishment in America: an annotated bibliography, 2007-2008 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - course materials- capital punishment in America: an annotated bibliography, 2007-2008 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - course materials- capital punishment in America: an annotated bibliography, 2007-2008 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Course materials- capital punishment seminar supplement, 2007 spring (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Course materials- capital punishment seminar supplement, 2009 spring (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Course materials- capital punishment seminar supplement, 2010 spring (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Course materials- capital punishment seminar supplement, 2005 fall (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Course materials- Constitutional criminal procedure (1995), Undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Course materials- Course supplement, 2008 spring (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Course materials- course supplement (Bound), 2008 spring (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Course materials- "The death penalty's strange career" (2002), Undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Course materials- "evidence of race discrimination in prosecutor jack McMahon's use of peremptory strikes in Common wealth v. Louis Montilla (1989), David Baldus (2003), Undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Course materials- "Gods justice and Ours", Antonin scalia(2002), Undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Course materials- "gresham's Law in reverse: Good service drives out bad"(2005), Undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Course materials- handout on race discrimination, 2008 Spring (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Course materials- "looney teens"(2005), Undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Course materials- narrative summaries of Exonerated Defendants, 2005 fall (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Course materials- Pennsylvania death penalty, 2008 spring (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Course materials- selections from Equal Justice and the death penalty: A legal and empirical analysis, David Bladus (1990), Undated (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Course materials- "Reflections on Death penalty law and practice since 1973: Steiker and steiker V. McCord, 2005 fall (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Course materials- "Reflections on Death penalty law and practice since 1973: Steiker and steiker V. McCord capital punishment class, 2007 spring (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Course materials- "reflections on death penalty law and practice Steiker and steiker V. McCord" (2003), Undated (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Course materials- ryan Commission report(2002), Undated (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Course materials- Seminar supplement, 2010 spring (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Course materials- Seminar supplement, 2010 spring (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Course materials- "the use of peremptory Challenges in Capital murder trials: A legal and empirical Analysis" David Baldus (2001), Undated (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Course Requirements and Outline, 2009 spring (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Criminal Culpability, 2004 fall (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Death penalty Appeals process, Undated (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Death penalty course suppliment form cathi Grosso (2006) used for Baldus's course material, Undated (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Death Penalty statutes, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - eariler introduction materials- teaching notes, 2002-2006 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Final exam, 2007 Spring (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Final Exam, 2008 spring (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - handout- capital punishment experiment, 1984 full (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Handout- Weems v. united States and early eighth ammendment cases, 2004 fall (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Handouts and course outlines, 2007 fall-2009 spring (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Rodney heemstra article, 2008 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Iowa Felony Murders, Undated (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Iowa Felony Murders, Undated (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - Iowa homicide supplement, Undated (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - Iowa Necessity Defense, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - ken Kress, overview Class, Undated (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - james Liebman class 13 readings, Undated (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - james Liebman class 13 readings, Undated (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - James Liebman class 16+17 readings, Undated (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - James liebman Class 19 readings, Undated (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - James liebman Class 20 readings, Undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - James liebman class 21 readings, Undated (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - James liebman class 21 readings, Undated (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - James liebman class 21 readings, Undated (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - James liebamn class 22 readings, Undated (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - James liebamn class 23 readings, Undated (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - James lieamn class 23 readings, Undated (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - mental illness defense, 1999; Undated (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - phyllis Nelson Case, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - New tork death penalty habeus corpus statute, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - prior student paper topics, 1997 Fall; 1999 fall (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - prior student paper topics, 2005 fall (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Procedural Due process, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Published Casebook- 2008 Supplement to cases and materials on the death penalty second edition (2008), Assignment for Capital punishment seminar, 2009 spring (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - questions- McClesky, 2002 Fall (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - michael L. Radelet syllabus, 2009 Spring (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Reading notes for Dead Man Walking by Helen Prejean, 1996 fall (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Reading Questions, 1999 fall; 2000 Fall; 2002 Fall (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Retired Material- Chapter 1, the debate, 2004; Undated (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - retired Material- Chapter 1, hard cases (?) notes, Undated (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Retired materials- Chapter 12, stays (?), Undated (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - retired- chapter 14, states bonus, 1994, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Retired materials- chapter 15, retractuity, 1998; 1999 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - retired materials- chapter 17 successive h(?), 2002; 2004 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Retired material- chapter 18, federal death penalty, Undated (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - retired material- chapter 19, international law, Undated (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - retired material- examination materials, 2005 fall (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - retired material- sister helen prejean, 1993; 1995; 1997; 2000 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - retired material- week 1 information, 2003; 2004 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Antonia scalia, Mario Cuomo and God, 2001; 2002 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Seminar handouts, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Seminar handouts, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - seminar requirements and student papers, 2007 fall (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - seminar requirements and student papers, 2007-2008 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - Seminar seating hart, 2006 fall; 2007 spring (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - state reports- "Guide to the New tork Assembly Death penalty hearings 2004-2005" by Eugene G. Wanger, Michigan Committee againest capital punishment, Undated (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - state reports- illinois: Governor's council on capital punishment, recommendations, Undated (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - State reports- Illinois: "Report of the governor's commission on capital punishment, Recommendation only" (April 2002) (original), Undated (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - Affirmative Defenses, 2002 Fall (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Blackboard material, syllabus, 2004 fall (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Brief Examples, 1997 fall; 1998 fall (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Common law, 1991 Fall; 1993 fall; 1996 fall; 1998 fall; 1999 fall (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Common Law, Undated (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Course materials- Course supplement, 2010 Spring (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Criminal Law, 1991-2010; 6.3; 1.7
    This subseries focuses around the Criminal Law course, including the syllabi, student papers, and a week by week layout of the course and the material that was covered.
    - State reports- Illinois "Report of the governor's commission on Capital punishment Recommendations only" (April) 2002 (photo copies), Undated (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - State reports- Illinois "Report of the governor's commission on Capital punishment " (April) 2002, Undated (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - State reports- "The status of the Death penalty in Illinois, as of January 13, 2003" Seminar task Force report: Murder and its Consequences (Fall 2002), Undated (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Student literature outlines, 2009 febuary (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Student paper comments, Undated (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Student paper- Aaron J. Shileny, "who's authority/ Justice scalia, capital punishment, and the catholic church", 2002 fall; 2003 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Student drafts with david Baldus comments, 2008 spring (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Student seminar paper outlines, 2008 spring (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Syllabi, 2007-2008 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - syllabi- ammended for weeks 11-14, 2009 Spring (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Syllabi- professor Baldus (with handwritten notes), 2011 spring (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - syllabi- capital punishment, proffesor Baldus, 2011 spring (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - syllabi- capital punishment, professor jim liebman, with Michael L. radelet syllabus from the university of Colorado, capital punishment in the United States, 2009 spring; 2009 fall (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - syllabi- death penalty, professor jim liebman (handwritten notes), 2009 fall (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Vair dice (?), Undated (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - week 1, 2007 fall- 2010 fall (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - week 1, 2010; Undated (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - week 1- habeus corpus, 2007; Undated (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - week 1- day 1 handout, 2007 spring; 2008 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - week 1- readings, 2011 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - week 1 and 2- assignments, 2005 fall (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - week 2- limit of arbitrariness, 2008 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - week 2- weems, etc., 2008 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - week 3- Individualization, 2208 spring (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - week 4- proportionally, 2007 spring (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - week4-readings, 2011 (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - week 5- Race, 2003 fall; 2005 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - week 5- readings, 2011 (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - week 5-race, 2008 (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - week 5 handout- "Race Discrimination and the adminstration of capital punishment", 2008 spring (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - week 6- ineffectiv assistance, 2003; Undated (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - week 6- readings, 2011 (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - week 8-readings, 2011 (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - week 7, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - week 7- death penalty, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - week 7- steiker and steiker V. McCord, 2003; 2005; 2007 (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - week 8- penalty trial, 1994; 2000; 2004; 2008 (Box 4, Folder 43)
    - week 8- prosecutions, Undated (Box 4, Folder 44)
    - week 9, Undated (Box 4, Folder 45)
    - week 9- Penalty trial continued, Undated (Box 4, Folder 46)
    - week 9-readings, 2011 (Box 4, Folder 47)
    - week 10- ring, Undated (Box 4, Folder 48)
    - week 11- jury selection, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 49)
    - week 11-ring(2002),gardner(1997),green, and payne(1991), Undated (Box 4, Folder 50)
    - Week 12- federal Habeus Corpus, Chapters 12 and 13, 2002; 2005 (Box 4, Folder 51)
    - Week 12- todd Pettys, 2006; 2007; 2008 (Box 4, Folder 52)
    - Week 12- readings, 2011 (Box 4, Folder 53)
    - Week 13, 2008; 2009 (Box 4, Folder 54)
    - week 13, 2009; Undated (Box 4, Folder 55)
    - week 13- reading federal habeus corpus, chapter 13 in published casebook, ca. 2009 spring (Box 4, Folder 56)
    - week 13- readings, 2011 (Box 4, Folder 57)
    - Week 13- review seminar, 2007 spring; 2008 spring; 2009 spring (Box 4, Folder 58)
    - week 13- teaching notes, 2003; Undated (Box 4, Folder 59)
    - week 13 and 14- Federal and international issues, 2000 Fall (Box 4, Folder 60)
    - Course materials- Course supplement, 2010 spring (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Course materials- Course supplement, 2010 spring (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Course materials- Course supplement, volume one, 2007 spring (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Course materials- Course supplement, volume one, 2007 spring (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Course materials- Course supplement, volume one, 2009 spring (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Course materials- Course supplement, volume two, 2007 spring (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Course materials- Course supplement, volume three (Weeks 11-14), 2004 Fall (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Course materials- Criminal Law, volume two, 2007 spring (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Course materials- Criminal Law of Iowa: Selected Statutory materials, 2000 fall (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Course materials- Criminal Law of Iowa: Selected Statutory materials, 2003 fall (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Course materials- Criminal law of Iowa: Selected Statutory materials, 2005 Fall; 2007 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Course materials- Criminal law of Iowa: Selected Statutory materials, 2005 spring (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Course materials- Criminal law of Iowa: Selected Statutory materials, 2009 Spring (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Course materials- Criminal law of Iowa: Selected Statutory materials, 2010 spring (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Course materials- syllabus, reading questions, and problems, 2003 fall (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Course outlines, 2003 fall; Undated (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Culpability requirements, Undated (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Death penalty experiment with students- poll of death penalty opinions before and after class, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Dudley and stevenson, necessity defence, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Eariler overheads, 1993 Fall (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Exams- Exam grades (Anonymous), 2005 December (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - exams- exam grades, participation points only (restricted), 2005 December (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Exams- Exam preview, 2002 Fall (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Exams- Exam preview, 2002 fall (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - exams- Exam questions and handwritten notes, 1999; 2000; Undated (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Exams- Final exam, 2003 Fall (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - exams- Final exam, 2004 fall (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Exams- Final exam, 2004 fall; 2005 fall (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Exams- final Exam, 2005 fall (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - exams- Final exam, answer key, 2009 spring (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Exams- final exam, essay, 2009 spring (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Exams- final exam essay question, 2005 fall (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - exams- final exam, multiple choice, 2009 fall (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - exams- final exam, multiple choice, 2009 spring (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Exams- final Practice questions, essay, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Exams- final exam, Rope questions, 2004 fall (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - Exams- practice exams, 1991 fall; 1992 fall; 2001 fall; Undated (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - Exams- Practice exams, 2001 spring; 2001 fall (Box 5, Folder 38)
    - Exams- practice exams, model penal code interpretation, 2001 fall (Box 5, Folder 39)
    - exams- Practice exam, perjury, Undated (Box 5, Folder 40)
    - Exams- Practice exqam, Mistake case, 2000 fall (Box 5, Folder 41)
    - Exams- problems overview, Undated (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - Exams- professor gary goodpaster final exam, 2013 fall (Box 5, Folder 43)
    - Exams- quiz, 1999 fall (Box 5, Folder 44)
    - exams- statutes covered, Undated (Box 5, Folder 45)
    - Exams- self defense, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 46)
    - First assignment- course materials, 2005 fall (Box 5, Folder 47)
    - Handout- criminal culpability, 2000 august (Box 5, Folder 48)
    - John Hinckley, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 49)
    - Icon, 2005 fall (Box 5, Folder 50)
    - Instructions for classroom 225, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 51)
    - Iowa law and fact issues, 2003; Undated (Box 5, Folder 52)
    - Iowa Sufficency of Evidence Case, State V. Oetkea, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 53)